studioabroad.com 2015-04-20

# Terra Dotta Privacy Policy

### 1\. STATEMENT.

Your privacy is important to you…and to us. So we'll protect the information you share with us. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information that Terra Dotta, LLC (“Terra Dotta”) receives and collects through its web site and related products and services, as well as some of the steps Terra Dotta has taken to protect this information. 

Terra Dotta adheres to the principles set forth in the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Terra Dotta has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Terra Dotta’s certification, please visit www.export.gov/safeharbor/.

### 2\. NOTICE.

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you register on our site or when you fill out our contact form, download a product, sign up for our newsletter or a webinar, or join a password-protected area of our site. We use your personal information to provide you with requested products and services, and to alert you to new products, special offers, updated information and other new services from Terra Dotta.

Terra Dotta may also record information about how individuals access our site. This information is typically not personally identifiable and may include internet protocol (IP) addresses (or the DNS name associated with it) of the individual's computer, the web site from which the individual linked to our site, and the browser software the individual is using to access our site. This information is used in the aggregate to administer computer systems and to make improvements to our site. 

Terra Dotta uses cookies and other technologies on our site for user session management and to provide a better user experience, including customization of content display. A cookie is text data that a website transfers to the individual's browser from a web server that is stored on the individual's computer hard drive. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify individuals.

### 3\. CHOICE.

If/When registration is available, you may choose not to register or provide personal information. You can still use most of terradotta.com. But you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

If/When registration is available, you may register to select the kinds of information you want to receive from us by subscribing to various services and communications, like our electronic newsletters. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding Terra Dotta products, programs, events, or services, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from Terra Dotta.

If/When Terra Dotta allows other companies to offer our registered customers information about their products and services, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing materials from third parties.

### 4\. ONWARD TRANSFER OF INFORMATION.

Terra Dotta will not disclose any personally identifiable information to a non-agent third party except as outlined in the Notice and Choice sections above. For third parties acting as Terra Dotta’s agent, Terra Dotta will use diligent efforts to confirm that the third party subscribes to the Safe Harbor principles, is subject to the EU Data Protection Directive, or has entered into an agreement with Terra Dotta that is consistent with the Safe Harbor principles.

### 5\. ACCESS.

Upon request, Terra Dotta will grant individuals reasonable access to personal information that it holds about them. In addition, Terra Dotta will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information that is shown to be inaccurate or incomplete.

### 6\. SECURITY.

Terra Dotta takes reasonable technical, administrative and physical measures to protect the security of your personal information from unauthorized use, disclosure and alteration.

When you place orders or access your personal account information, you're utilizing a secure connection via SSL, which encrypts your personal information before it's sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available.

Terra Dotta provides information and training to all employees who have access to personally identifiable data maintained by Terra Dotta, and Terra Dotta employees are responsible for the internal security of such information.

Terra Dotta will not process personally identifiable information in any way that is incompatible or inconsistent with the purpose for which such information was collected. 

Terra Dotta takes all reasonable measures to ensure that such information is reliable for its intended use, and is accurate, complete and current.

Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. 

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not share these with others.

### 7\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY.

Terra Dotta does not knowingly collect or maintain information acquired through our site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of the site or services is directed to persons under 13 years of age. Any user under 13 years of age should not use or access our site at any time or in any manner. If Terra Dotta learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected from our site without verified parental consent, then Terra Dotta will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

### 8\. WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE.

When you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address, we may use this information to send you updates about our site, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our service, and announcements about new services that we offer. When you order from us, we ask for your credit card number and billing address. We use this information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that time. For your convenience, we do save billing information in case you want to order from us again, but we don't use this information without your permission.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, and answering customer questions about products or services. We only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Terra Dotta will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served on Terra Dotta or the site, or in response to governmental orders, subpoenas, search warrants, or other governmental request; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Terra Dotta and its family of Web sites, and, (c) protect the personal safety, rights and property of Terra Dotta, users of Terra Dotta Web sites, or others.

### 9. DISPUTE RESOLUTION.

Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of personal information should be directed to Terra Dotta pursuant to the contact information below. Terra Dotta will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy.

Terra Dotta agrees that disputes that cannot be resolved after good faith discussions may be referred to the American Arbitration Association for resolution by binding arbitration.

### 10. IN THE EVENT OF MERGER, SALE, OR BANKRUPTCY.

In the event that all or part of Terra Dotta is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, Terra Dotta may transfer or assign the personally identifiable information held by Terra Dotta as part of such merger, acquisition, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of Terra Dotta's bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, Terra Dotta may not be able to control how personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

### 11. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically by Terra Dotta, as reflected by the "last updated" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes.

### 12. CONTACT INFORMATION.

Terra Dotta welcomes questions and comments regarding this Privacy Policy. We may be contacted at info@terradotta.com.

Last Updated: October 7, 2013
